top100gamesites.com 2012-08-29

# Game - Top 100 Sites

## Privacy Statement for Top100gameSites.com

CKSinfo(CKS Computer Service Ltd.) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Top100gameSites.com. 

This site contains links to other sites. Top100gameSites.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control provided by our Service Provider. 

**Children's Guidelines**  
Our Web Site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program. We do:  
\- NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent  
\- NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent  
\- NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent  
\- NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent  
\- NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.  
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: bizATckscomputerserviceltd.com (change "AT" to @)
